# **George Brata**

Frontend Web Developer





## Summary

Versatile frontend web developer with broad experience using all kinds of JS frameworks, but my favorite stack (currently) is **Vue.js** and **Nuxt.js**. I am passionate about education, the Internet, and blockchain technology - and everything that connects the three.

# Experience

Mar 2022 - Present

### Senior Vue.js Freelancer, BinarCode

Designed, implemented, tested and documented frontend functionalities of a web-based job management platform using Vue.js, Tailwind, Pinia, FormKit, ElementIO and Netlify.

lan 2021 - Mar 2022

#### Senior Vue.js Developer, SHE Information Technology

My responsibilities were maintaining a web platform based on FirstSpirit CMS, creating new Vue.js components with Bootstrap and providing support for multilingual content teams.

Jul 2018 - Dec 2019

#### Frontend Web Developer, **QCatalyst**

Building, testing, deploying and maintaining responsive consumer-facing web applications for National Geographic using modern technologies like React, Redux, Tailwind, Webpack, Storybook, Cypress and Docker.

#### Ul Developer, 3Pillar Global

Apr 2017 - Apr 2018

Developed financial education learning modules for a US-based client in a React.js app. As a team, we worked with tools like Github, CircleCl, JIRA, Browserstack and Confluence to deliver high-quality readable code and documentation.

lan 2016 - Apr 2017

#### Junior Web Developer, Yonder

Migrated a legacy app from Microsoft Silverlight to AngularJS and built the frontend of a completely new web app from scratch using Angular.js and Bulma CSS.

Feb 2016 - present

#### Trainer, Digital Kids Cluj-Napoca

In my spare time I teach children the computer skills they need to thrive in the 21st century, including the basics of programming, photo/video editing, robotics, web development and other digital abilities.

## Education

2014 - 2015 2010 - 2014 Computer Science, *Babes-Bolyai University*, Cluj-Napoca Mathematics - Informatics, *Emanuil Gojdu* High School, Oradea

# Why hire me?

Results-driven and people-oriented, I am feeling most comfortable in agile, fast-paced development environments. My passion is crafting modern web applications with great UX. Beside my regular frontend developer job, over the last 6 years I have built several freelancing <u>side-projects</u> and I went to a <u>dozen hackathons</u> to train those muscles.